htmlblock.co.uk 2006-09-24

# htmlblock.co.uk - privacy statement for www.htmlblock.co.uk

**General Privacy Statement** HTMLBlock has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.htmlblock.co.uk.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

The www.htmlblock.co.uk website may use cookies, which are small text files on your computer. A cookie contains identifying information. The cookie is used to make the link between you and the information you have provided to the website. This allows your shopping basket to be kept separate from other users and enables us to automatically complete some of the forms when you subsequently use them. The creation of a cookie on your computer does not give the website any access to other information such as your email address.

The European Union Directive on Privacy and Electronic Communications (the "Directive"), which came into force on 31st July 2002, recognizes that cookies are a "legitimate and useful tool" for many activities, including verifying the identity of web site users. The Directive makes it compulsory for websites to inform users if cookies are being used, and to provide some information on how cookies are used. The www.htmlblock.co.uk website (in common with most other shopping websites) will not work without cookies.

Our site's registration form requires you to provide us with some contact information (e.g. name and email address). We sometimes use this contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company and our products and services. This contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. If at any time you receive unwanted information from HTMLBlock please contact us and we will remove you from our records.

This site contains links to other sites. www.htmlblock.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

In some cases, we work with other companies to provide products and services. In such cases we will never share your details directly with another company.

Our site uses a form to help us manage requests. We collect contact information (like email address). Contact information is used to respond to enquiries, or get in touch with you when necessary.

Our online surveys ask for contact information (like email address). We use contact information from our surveys to send information about our company.

We run competitions on our site in which we ask for contact information (like email address). We use contact information from competitions to send information about our company. Contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Any other information is shared only within HTMLBlock.

**Public Forums**

This site may include chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All instances of unauthorised attempted access to our site are logged and investigated. Where necessary HTMLBlock will inform law enforcement agencies or other relevant organisations regarding misconduct.

**Email**

At HTMLBlock we respect the privacy of email accounts and we store your email addresses just as securely as other information on HTMLBlock.co.uk. We will not send you unwanted email messages or junk mail, and your details will not be passed to ANY organisation beyond HTMLBlock without your explicit permission.

However, We may use email to keep you up to date with news about products, services and offers that we think maybe are of interest to you. If you do not want to be kept informed in this way by email, please let us know. You can do this by ticking the relevant box where your email address is stored when you register or by choosing the unsubscribe option within the email.

**What information do you collect from you?** When you visit our site we system will automatically collect together and log in our database your IP Address, Where you came from, trace which pages you visit and how long you spend on them. Which browser you are using and which operating system you use. Who your ISP is and keywords you used to reach us if you came from a search engine. The only reason for this log is so that we can carry out statistics of who visits our site so that we can make improvements as and when needed!

We DO NOT collect personal information, e.g. your name, address, phone number, credit card numbers, etc...

**When you we have hold of your personal information and is it safe from others?** We only hold personal information if you purchase a product from our site. This information is kept in PayPal's database and the only people who have access to them is ourselves and PayPal. So any information we hold is 100% safe from other online users!

**For more information please read our terms and conditions.** If you would like to know any other information regarding our Privacy statement please feel free to contact us at any time where one of our members of staff will be happy to help!  
read our terms and conditions. 

Contact The Support Team. **  
**
